let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who is the Sencho of Heart Pirates?",
    answer: "Trafalgar D. Water Law",
    options: [
      "Monkey D. Luffy",
      "Trafalgar D. Water Law",
      "Eustass Kid",
      "Bartolomeo",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is Sanji's Family Name?",
    answer: "Vinsmoke",
    options: ["Nefertari", "Charlette", "Vinsmoke", "Kuja"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which Devil Fruit that Ace Eat?",
    answer: "Mera Mera No mi",
    options: [
      "Mera Mera No mi",
      "Gomu Gomu No mi",
      "Pika Pika No mi",
      "Op Op No mi",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the Name of the Island Whale that Straw Hats Met?",
    answer: "Laboon",
    options: ["Hattori", "Eyelashes", "Karoo", "Laboon"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which Devil Fruit that Nico Robin Eat?",
    answer: "Hana Hana No mi",
    options: [
      "Hana Hana No mi",
      "Hito Hito no Mi",
      "Bara Bara no Mi",
      "Suna Suna no Mi",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Name the Emperor whom Luffy fight first?",
    answer: "Big Mom",
    options: ["WhiteBeard", "Shanks", "Big Mom", "Kaido"],
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the Name of the Devil Fruit that Aokiji ate?",
    answer: "Hie Hie no Mi",
    options: [
      "Yami Yami no Mi",
      "Hie Hie no Mi",
      "Mochi Mochi no Mi",
      "Goro Goro no Mi",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who is the Founder of Revolutionary Army?",
    answer: "Dragon",
    options: ["Dragon", "Ivanko", "Kuma", "Hack"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who is the Vice Leader of Revolutionary Army?",
    answer: "Sabo",
    options: ["Koala", "Hack", "Sabo", "Ivanko"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How many levels are there in Impel Down?",
    answer: "6",
    options: ["7", "5", "6", "4"],
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What is the Bounty of Luffy When he took down Arlong?",
    answer: "30 Million Berries",
    options: [
      "10 Million Berries",
      "30 Million Berries",
      "15 Million Berries",
      "20 Million Berries",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What is the First Bounty of Chopper?",
    answer: "50 Berries",
    options: ["100 Berries", "500 Berries", "50 Berries", "150 Berries"],
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Who is the Chief of CP 9?",
    answer: "Spandom",
    options: ["Spandom", "Luchi", "Kaku", "Blueno"],
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Who has High Priority to give order to Seraphism?",
    answer: "Elders",
    options: ["Veagapunk", "Elders", "Sentemaru", "CP0"],
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What is the Name of the Stones with Ancient text?",
    answer: "Poneglyphs",
    options: ["City of Gold", "Pluton", "Poneglyphs", "None of the Above"],
  },
];
